The craziest thing is, this is the
closest to understanding who I am.
More than 99.5.
% of the people I know.
Number one.
But okay, number one was the origin.
This message that I'm talking about, the
reason it's in random letters is because
it was a message that I sent to my friend.
And it was back in 2020.
And he was my best friend at the time.
It was one of the toughest
moments of my life.
It was the time my grandfather
died and I didn't know who to tell.
I, I say it in here where I'm like, I,
I feel like I have a hole in my heart.
Because I was thinking about all the
memories that I felt like were deleted.
My grandfather died and it, it felt hopeless.
It felt, why this is on here is
because that moment, that death of my
grandfather changed everything in my life.
Because he was the one person in
my life who respected me way, way,
way more than I respected myself.
And.
In that moment, I felt like, if I
didn't respect myself to the same
extent that he did, even after he
died, then I'm truly letting him die.
Because I, and, once that thought came into
my mind, I just, I knew that I had to change.
And I had to change drastically.
And, the start of that was respecting myself.
Always origin a stories  start
with someone dying don't they.
But number two,
what should I even name number two?
Insecurities and growth.
This guy.
Y'all must know healthy gamer, bro.
Um